(Sheldon:)President Seibert, I don't
know why you're yelling.
(Sheldon:)You're the one who
made me go on the radio.
(Sheldon:)I was expecting a professional
science interview,
(Sheldon:)not an attack by some
morning zoo shock jock.
(Sheldon:)Well, if the university
needs money so badly,
(Sheldon:)perhaps you should
start a swear jar.
Whoa! That one's worth a dollar.
(Amy:)I know you don't like it,
(Amy:)but every time
you do an interview,
(Amy:)it raises the profile
of the university.
(Amy:)That translates to funding.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, well, I'm not just
(Sheldon:)some trained monkey
dancing for coins.
(Leonard:)Of course you're not.
(Leonard:)People love trained monkeys.
(Penny:)How can you not be happy?
(Penny:)You're tall, thin and famous.
(Penny:)Oh, my God,
I'm jealous of Sheldon.
Lock, you're going to be
doing this stuff for a while.
You're just going to have to find
a way to get used to it.
(Sheldon:)But none of you know
what this is like.
(Sheldon:)Being celebrated for something
you wish you never did.
(Penny:)You clearly haven't been with me
at Mardi Gras.